http://www.sunrosearomatics.com/shopcontent.asp?type=privacy

Shopping Cart Items: 0
Sub-Total :
Contact
Jewelry...
Silver Perfume Necklaces
Gift Ideas...
Travel Chest
Essential Oils...
Wild Crafted Essential Oils
Carrier Oils & Blends...
Anointing
Bath & Body...
Butters
Culinary...
Herbs & Spices
Tea & Teapots
Diffusers & Blends...
Passive Diffusers
Himalaya Salt Products...
Holistic Synergies
Incense...
Aromatic Woods
Baiedio Incense
Resins
Media...
Aromatherapy Acology Today...
CDs
Essential Herbal Magazine...
Video Library
Metaphysical...
Chakra Balancing
Palm Stones
Worry Stones
Perfumery...
Contact
Please review our Shipping and Policies before ordering. We ship to USA addresses only at this time.
Home  »  Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
We understand the importance of privacy and security with regard to shopping online. As such, we respect your right to privacy. All detailed client information is held in confidence, and is never sold, transferred, shared or solicited to other parties. Please note the following:
Asking for your information
On occasion, we may ask our customers for personal information such as your name, address, company name, e-mail address and other details. Providing us with your information simply helps us to better serve our clientele and process orders more efficiently. In the event we ask you to share other personal information with us over the Internet, we will always inform you as to how we will use the information.
Email Addresses
We understand the importance of privacy and security with regard to email addresses. As such, we respect your right to privacy. No one wants junk mail or spam. All detailed client information is held in confidence, and is never sold, transferred, shared or solicited to other parties. If you receive SRA Newsletter in error, please inform us and we will remove your name from our distribution list.
Personal Information Privacy
SunRose Aromatics will take all necessary steps to keep your personal information confidential. Those steps include limiting access to informational databases, encrypting sensitive information and securing our data with appropriate passwords and user permissions.
As stated above, SunRose Aromatics will not sell, rent, or share our customers' personal information to other companies for any reason.
We will communicate with clients via e-mail or other online delivery devices only if the client agrees to receive those communications. If you believe that you are receiving our communications in error or no longer desire to receive them, please inform us and we will remove your name from our distribution lists.
Order Information Privacy and Security
SunRose Aromatics currently uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to safeguard your information, including your credit card information, during all phases of online transactions. None of the people who have made purchases through SunRose Aromatics' web site using SSL, have reported fraudulent use of their credit card as a result of a previous online order. If you are not comfortable sending your credit card information online, please
e-mail a sales representative call you to complete the order, or give us a call at 207.342.2046 and speak us direct.
NEVER include your credit card number or other sensitive information in unencrypted e-mail. In the extremely unlikely event that we ever do suspect a client's credit card number has been intercepted, we will immediately notify the client.
Cookies
SunRose Aromatics does not use cookies.
How To Contact Us
If you have any comments on this policy, our use of your information, SSL, Cookies or other Privacy issues, please don't hesitate to
contact us.
HOLIDAY DELIVERIES
If you are shipping gifts or purchasing to create gifts, please allow time to get your packages in a timely fashion.
West Coast by the 11th.
East Coast by the 14th.
If you are unsure, feel free to contact us.
Products
Jewelry...
Chakra Jewelry
Gemstone Bracelets
Handmade Terra Cotta Pendants
Jade Jewelry
Pewter & Glass Pendants
Pewter Pendants
Silver Perfume Necklaces
Gift Ideas...
Gift Certificates
Gift Sets
Gifts for Her
Gifts for Him
Gifts for the Fitness Enthusiast
Gifts for the Perfumer
Gifts Under $100
Gifts Under $25
Gifts Under $50
Gifts Under $75
Travel Chest
Essential Oils...
Absolutes
CO2 Extracts
Lavenders
Organic Essential Oils
Rare & Exotic Oils
Single Notes 10% Dilutions
Wild Crafted Essential Oils
Carrier Oils & Blends...
Carrier Oils
Infused Oils
Organic Carrier Oils
Professional Formulas
SuppliesHydrosolsWhat's NewAnointingBath & Body...
All Natural Perfumes
Aromatic Soaps
Face Care
Foaming Soaps
Hair Care
Massage Oils
Men's Care
Salt Scrubs
ButtersCulinary...
Herbs & Spices
Tea & Teapots
Diffusers & Blends...
Diffuser Blend Sets
Diffuser Blends
Candle Diffusers
Electric Diffusers
Passive Diffusers
Himalaya Salt Products...
Himalaya Salt Crystals
Himalaya Salt Deodorant
Himalaya Salt Purifying Bars
Himalaya Salt Scrubs
Himalayan Gourmet Salt
Holistic SynergiesIncense...
Aromatic Woods
Baiedio Incense
Resins
Media...
Aromatherapy Acology Today...
Aromatherapy Acology Today - Current Issue
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2017
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2016
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2015
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2014
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2013
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2012
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2011
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2010
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2009
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2008
Aromatherapy Acology Today - 2007
Books
CDs
Essential Herbal Magazine...
Essential Herbal Magazine - Current Issue
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2016
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2015
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2014
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2013
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2012
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2011
Essential Herbal Magazine - 2010
Video Library
Metaphysical...
Chakra Balancing
Palm Stones
Worry Stones
Perfumery...
Perfumery Kits
Base Notes
Middle Notes
Top Notes
Perfumer's Supplies
SeminarsPCHS
Featured Products
Enchanted Forest Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
Queen Rhiannon Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
Sensuality Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
Sweet Dreams Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
Work Out/Muscle Relief Massage Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
Vanilla Lovers Fantasy Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
Serenity Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
Please make selection below.
Details
5ml Clary Sage Extra France
$16.30
Details
PreviousNext
Enchanted Forest Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
In our Professional Formula # 3 as the base:
Rice Bran Refined, Fractionated Coconut Oil, Rosehip Seed (O), Evening Primrose & Vitamin E.
Blended essential oils of:
Patchouli, Clary sage, Spikenard, Oak Moss
Revitalize your senses with the earthly scents of this blend. The magic of the forest .. dappled with light.
Patchouli unites all levels of your life The rejuvenating properties of Patchouli makes it highly recommended for mature skin. Clary sage provides clarity & restores harmony to your life by stimulating & grounding your mind. Spikenard is known as the ultimate essential oil to find inner balance in the emotional & physical interplay of energies.
Please make selection below.
Details
Queen Rhiannon Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
In our Professional Formula # 5 as the base:
Apricot Kernel, Rice Bran Refined, Rosehip Seed, Evening Primrose, Arnica Infused & Vitamin E.
Blended essential oils of:
Lavender, Marjoram Wild, Clary Sage, Chamomile Roman & Vetivert
The name Rhiannon literally means 'Great Queen'. Also known as the Horse Goddess.
Lavender to create your own 'protected space'
where you can feel uninhibited and free
to be all that you want to be. Marjoram has been known to be effective for
muscular aches and pains. Chamomile Roman said to assist in letting go of emotional worries, a wonderful relaxant. Also said to ease muscular aches and pains. Vetiver is known to recharge your emotional and physical energies and support you through life.
Please make selection below.
Details
Sensuality Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
In our Professional Formula # 4 as the base:
Apricot Kernel Oil, Fractionated Coconut Oil,
Rosehip Seed (O), Evening Primrose (O)  & Vitamin E.
Blended essential oils:
Sweet Orange (O), Ylang Ylang Extra, Patchouli & Nutmeg
A delicious blend that your skin will drink up.
Your skin will be like velvet to touch.
Please make selection below.
Details
Sweet Dreams Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
In our Professional Formula # 3 as the base:
Rice Bran Refined, Fractionated Coconut Oil, Rosehip Seed (O), Evening Primrose & Vitamin E.
Blended essential oils of:
Lavender, Marjoram Sweet & Lemon (O)
Lavender has been known and preferred when dealing with insomnia, especially
when due to mental stress.
It soothes and harmonises the emotions. Marjoram has been said to ease nervous tension & insomnia. Lemon is said to clear the mind very effectively & can be very calming for those who are emotionally overwrought.
Please make selection below.
Details
Work Out/Muscle Relief Massage Oil
Fractionated Coconut, Arnica Infused in Sunflower Oil, Essential oils of Lavender, Marjoram Wild, Rosemary, Black Pepper, Peppermint & Vit E.
Please make selection below.
Details
Vanilla Lovers Fantasy Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
In our Professional Formula # 5 Base:
Apricot Kernel, Rice Bran Refined, Rosehip Seed Organic, Evening Primrose, Arnica Infused & Vitamin E.
Blended Oils of:
Vanilla Infused and Patchouli.
The wonderful scent of Vanilla has been found to reduce stress. Producing a calm and positive feeling.
Evoking pleasant childhood memories, sweet treats, innocent pleasures.
Please make selection below.
Details
Serenity Massage & After Bath & Body Oil
In our Professional Formula #3 as the base:
Rice Bran Refined, Fractionated Coconut Oil, Rosehip Seed (O), Evening Primrose & Vitamin E.
Blended essential oils of ~ Geranium and Lavender
Soothing to the skin as well as moisturizing.
Geranium - Lifts the spirits.
* A tonic to the circulation
Lavender - Soothes the Spirit.
* Valuable for most skin conditions.
Great after bath and a wonderful massage oil.
Please make selection below.
Aroma Power: Maine business imports essential oils from around the world.READ FULL ARTICLE
is a Proud Member of:
